Guide to the Helen A. Fraser papers, 1918-1962.
Fraser, Helen A. papers, 1918-1962.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Helen A. Fraser papers, 1918-1962.
1975
Helen Anderson, Fraser 1902-
c. 20.4 c.f.
Correspondence, printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, notes, reports, newsletters, press releases, programs, broadsides and other items pertaining to Ms. Fraser's interest in the Albany Inter-Racial Council, the New York State Commission Against Discrimination, Unitarian Church work, other civic organizations, and health insurance plans, folklore, and other topics.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Medical librarian.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, notes, reports, newsletters, press releases, programs, broadsides and other items pertaining to Ms. Fraser's interest in the Albany Inter-Racial Council, the New York State Commission Against Discrimination, Unitarian Church work, other civic organizations, and health insurance plans, folklore, and other topics.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Fraser, Helen Anderson,1902-; Albany Inter-Racial Council.; New York State Commission Against Discrimination.; Unitarian Churches.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collection #2460 and #2702.
Includes collection #2460 and #2702.
Includes collection #2460 and #2702.
Series XV
- 224 State fund Requests (Box 59, Folder 1)
- 224 State fund Requests (Box 59, Folder 1)
- State fiscal year folders(missing state years 1941-1952;1954;1955;1957-1958;1961;1962;1967), 1939-1968 (Box 59, Folder 2-11)
- State fiscal year folders(missing state years 1972 and 1976), 1970-1979 (Box 59, Folder 12-20)
- State fiscal year folders, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 21-30)
- State fiscal year folders, 1990-1994 (Box 59, Folder 31-35)
- State fiscal year folder, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 36)
- State fiscal year folders, 1996-2001 (Box 59, Folder 37-42)
- NYC Extension Association Law, 1957-1959 (Box 59, Folder 43)
- 224b Area Specialists Program, 1988-1994 (Box 59, Folder 44-45)
- CCE Budgets and Letters, 1929-1998 (Box 59, Folder 46)
- Budget and letter folders for each year, 1969-1979 (Box 59, Folder 47-56)
- Budget and letter folders for each year, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 57-66)
- Budget and letter folders for each year, 1990-1999 (Box 60, Folder 1-9)
- CCE budget requests to Deans, 1972,1974,1977 and 1996 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- CCE System trends and other charts, 1954-2004 (Box 60, Folder 11-16)
- CCE Association Funds History (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Association EFNEP Funds History, 1969-2000 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- CCE Association letters to President-budget info, 1968-2001 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- CCE Association MOA budget info, 1966-2000 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- CCE Association letters-other than budget, 1960-1993 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Includes detailed listing of what is in folders 2-6 and 1949 report "Program of State Leaders of County Agriculture Agents", 1949-2000 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Various publications, 1960-1968 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Various publications, 1975-1978 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Various publications, 1981-1989 (Box 60, Folder 25-27)
- Various publications, 1990-1998 (Box 60, Folder 28-29)
- Various publications, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Regional programs, 1969-1991 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
- Area program agreements between Cornell and CCE Associations, 1967-1990 (Box 61, Folder 3-29)